{
    "questionnair": [
        {
            "question": "What is the app you are building ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "start",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "I am building API",
                    "next": "typeofchange",
                    "score": "1"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "I am building UI",
                    "next": "typeofchange",
                    "score": "2"
                }
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "Is this for a new micro service / existing that is not in use ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "typeofchange",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "Yes, changes are not yet live",
                    "next": "",
                    "score": "1"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "This is real stuff",
                    "next": "zone",
                    "score": "2"
                }
            ]
        },

        {
            "question": "What Zone you are deploying ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "zone",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "Deploying Zone 2",
                    "next": "database",
                    "score": "2"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Depoying to Zone 3",
                    "next": "database",
                    "score": "1"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you have database migration ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "database",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "Yes",
                    "next": "database-size",
                    "score": "2"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "No",
                    "next": "consumers",
                    "score": "1"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is your database size ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "database-size",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "BIG",
                    "next": "consumers",
                    "score": "5"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "SMALL",
                    "next": "consumers",
                    "score": "1"
                }
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "question": "How many consumers do you have ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "consumers",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "More than 3+",
                    "next": "usage",
                    "score": "5"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Internal Domain Only",
                    "next": "usage",
                    "score": "1"
                }
            ]
        }

        ,
        {
            "question": "Does every consumer card application need your service ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "usage",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "Yes",
                    "next": "backwardcompatibility",
                    "score": "5"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "No",
                    "next": "backwardcompatibility",
                    "score": "1"
                }
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "question": "Are you taking any fields out of API  ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "backwardcompatibility",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "No / Does not apply",
                    "next": "newfunctionality",
                    "score": "0"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Yes",
                    "next": "consumer-notification",
                    "score": "2"
                }
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "question": "Did you talk to consumers to ensure usages is removed ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "consumer-notification",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "No.",
                    "next": "didnottalktoconsumers",
                    "score": "0"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Yes",
                    "next": "",
                    "score": "2"
                }
            ]
        }

        ,
        {
            "question": "Go talk to the consumers and come back.",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "didnottalktoconsumers",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "Nothing to click.",
                    "next": "",
                    "score": "0"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Nothing to click",
                    "next": "",
                    "score": "0"
                }
            ]
        }

        ,
        {
            "question": "Does this change for a new funtionalty going live ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "newfunctionality",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "Yes.",
                    "next": "rampup",
                    "score": "2"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "No",
                    "next": "",
                    "score": "-10"
                }
            ]
        }

        ,
        {
            "question": "Is there a ramp-up strategy ?",
            "rank": "1",
            "id": "rampup",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "Yes.",
                    "next": "rampup",
                    "score": "1"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "No",
                    "next": "",
                    "score": "5"
                }
            ]
        }
        ,
        {
            "question": "No More Questions",
            "rank": "",
            "id": "",
            "choice": [
                {
                    "answer": "------",
                    "next": "",
                    "score": ""
                },
                {
                    "answer": "------",
                    "next": "",
                    "score": ""
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
